Wang Xiangzhai used to say
Zhan Zhuang (Post Standing) is the training of stupid kung fu
A smart person often fails in hurrying up
Modern science has certified this
Muscle memory requires 21 days
It takes 90 days to truly form an instinctive reaction
Those who complain that Zhang Zhuang has no result
Most of them failed as go fishing 3 days and dry net for 2 days, not persistent.
Isn't not to compare who can stand longer
It's the process of talking to your own body
When you let go of your mind
Treat each exercise as a journey of exploring the body
Naturally, you can surpass a big gap
between thinking it to be correct and being wrong once you do it
If you're interested in Zhan Zhuang
Please contact the teacher, the teacher will teach you